<?xml version="1.0"?>
<exam>
<title>IT Essentials (ITE v6.0)</title>

<!-- Hoofdstuk 1 -->
<!-- Vraag 1 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What are two factors that must be considered when choosing
a computer case? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>the size of the monitor</item>
<item>the speed of the memory</item>
<item goed="ja">the number of internal drive locations</item>
<item goed="ja">the size of the motherboard and the power supply</item>
<item>the number of LED indicators at the front of the case</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
<p>
De monitor is een apparaat compleet onafhankelijk van de computerkast.
Werkgeheugen komt in kleine modules die direct op het moederbord
geprikt worden, deze staan niet in contact met de behuizing.
Een grotere kast zal meer sloten hebben voor schijfstations.
Er zijn meerdere formaten PSU en moederbord. Deze hebben op de juiste
plekken in de behuizing ruimte en schroeven nodig. Daarom is het
dus van belang een behuizing te gebruiken die overeenkomt met
de PSU en moederbord.
</p>
<p>
De LED indicatoren op de computerbehuizing zal niet veel verschillen
per behuizing en is ook niet essentieel voor het gebruik van de
computer.
</p>
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 2 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
<p>
A technician looks at a motherboard and sees a 24-pin connector. What
component would connect to the motherboard through the use of this 24-pin
connector?
</p>
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">power supply</item>
<item>video card</item>
<item>PATA optical drive</item>
<item>SATA drive</item>
<item>floppy drive</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
<p>
De 24-pin connector is de voornaamste stroomleverancier voor het
moederbord.
</p>
<p>
Een videokaart zal aangesloten worden op een PCIe, AGP of PCI slot.
</p>
</toelichting>
<tags>
<tag>floppy drive</tag>
<tag>PATA</tag>
<tag>optical drive</tag>
<tag>SATA</tag>
<tag>video card</tag>
<tag>PSU</tag>
</tags>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 3 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What electrical unit refers to the number of
electrons moving through a circuit per second?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">current</item>
<item>voltage</item>
<item>resistance</item>
<item>power</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 4 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What characteristic of electricity is expressed in watts?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
the amount of work required to move electrons through a circuit
</item>
<item>the resistance to the flow of current in a circuit</item>
<item>the amount of electrons flowing through a circuit per second</item>
<item goed="ja">
the work required to move electrons through a circuit multiplied
by the number of electrons flowing through a circuit per second
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 5 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>Which type of memory is primarily used as cache memory?</vraag>
<choice>
<item>DRAM</item>
<item>RAM</item>
<item>ROM</item>
<item goed="ja">SRAM</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
Cache geheugen wordt intern in de processor gebruikt veel gebruikte
secties van het DRAM werkgeheugen te schaduwen voor snelle toegang. Dit
geheugen moet dus sneller zijn dan het DRAM werkgeheugen, maar mag een
stuk kleiner en dus duurder per bit zijn. Hiervoor wordt SRAM gebruikt,
wat opgebouwd is uit meerdere transistoren voor een bit geheugen. Bij
DRAM wordt een bit geheugen bewaard in een enkele condensator. Dit maakt
veel grotere hoeveelheden geheugen mogelijk, maar is dus een langere
toegangstijd. ROM geheugen is niet direct schrijfbaar, alleen te lezen.
Dit is uiteraard ongeschikt als cache geheugen, maar wordt gebruikt om
firmware zoals het BIOS in op te slaan.
</toelichting>
<tags>
<tag>cache geheugen</tag>
<tag>DRAM</tag>
<tag>ROM</tag>
<tag>ROM</tag>
<tag>SRAM</tag>
</tags>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 6 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
<img src="exams/nic.jpg"/>
<p>
Refer to the exhibit. Which type of adapter is shown?
</p>
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>sound</item>
<item>RAID</item>
<item>video</item>
<item goed="ja">network interface</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
De RJ45 aansluiting is de meest overtuigende aanwijzing dat het
hier om een netwerkkaart gaat. Hier wordt een acht polige twisted-pair
kabel op aangesloten. De twee leds staan voor transmit (TX) en receive (RX).
Ook is een netwerkkaart al jarenlang erg smal, zoals de kaart in de
afbeelding.
</toelichting>
<tags>
<tag>RJ45</tag>
<tag>RAID</tag>
<tag>video</tag>
</tags>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 7 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which component controls the communications and interactions between the
CPU and other components on the motherboard?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>RAM</item>
<item>BIOS</item>
<item>CMOS</item>
<item goed="ja">Chipset</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 8 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two activities are normally controlled by the Northbridge part
of the chipset? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>communication between the CPU and the I/O ports</item>
<item goed="ja">access to the RAM</item>
<item>communication between the CPU and the hard drive</item>
<item goed="ja">access to the video card</item>
<item>communication between the CPU and the sound card</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
<p>
In systemen met een North- Southbridge architectuur wordt de Northbridge
gebruikt voor onderdelen die snelle toegang nodig hebben tot de processor. De
Northbridge is dan ook, in tegenstelling tot de Southbridge, direct
verbonden met de processor. Er zijn twee onderdelen die snelle toegang
tot de processor vereisen: het werkgeheugen (RAM) en in mindere mate
de videokaart. Alleen AGP videokaarten zijn met de Northbridge verbonden.
</p>
<p>
De Southbridge is zorgt voor dingen als de PCI bus. Hier zit bijvoorbeeld
de geluidskaart en opslag als harde-schijven op, en PCI videokaarten. Niet
alle videokaarten zijn dus verbonden met de Northbridge. I/O poorten zijn
uiteindelijk ook verbonden met de PCI bus en de Southbridge met enkele
tussenschakels.
</p>
<p>
Tegenwoordig worden functies van de Northbridge echter direct geimplementeerd
in de processor. De AMD Athlon 64 uit 2004 bijvoorbeeld deed dit al. De
traditionele North- Southbridge architectuur is dus feitelijk komen te
vervallen in hedendaagse computersystemen.
</p>
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 9 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which unit of measurement is used to indicate the hard drive speed?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">revolutions per minute</item>
<item>gigabytes</item>
<item>pages per minute</item>
<item>clusters per minute</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
"Revolutions per minute" is een maat voor de draaisnelheid van een
harde-schijf. Hieruit kun je echter nog niet de doorvoersnelheid
en toegangssnelheid opmaken, hoewel een hogere draaisnelheid in de
regel in een snellere toegangssnelheid betekent.
Een gigabyte is een eenheid voor de grote van data. Een gigabyte (GiB)
staat voor 2^30 bytes. Een gigabyte aangeduid als GB kan voor
10^9 of 2^30 bytes staan, dus let op.
"Pages per minute" en "clusters per minute" zijn geen bestaande termen.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 10 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which type of interface was originally developed for high-definition televisions
and is also popular to use with computers to connect audio and video devices?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>FireWire</item>
<item>DVI</item>
<item goed="ja">HDMI</item>
<item>USB</item>
<item>VGA</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
FireWire en USB zijn beide vergelijkbare seriele interfaces voor dataoverdracht. DVI
en VGA zijn respectievelijk een digitale en analoge standaard voor monitoren, geen
van beide ondersteunen geluid. HDMI ondersteund wel geluid, het videosignaal van HDMI
is identiek aan DVI.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 11 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two devices are considered input devices? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">biometric authentication device</item>
<item>printer</item>
<item goed="ja">digital camera</item>
<item>projector</item>
<item>speakers</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 12 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is indicated by the contrast ratio of a monitor?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
the difference in the intensity of light between the brightest
white and darkest black that can be displayed
</item>
<item>how often the picture image is refreshed</item>
<item>the total number of pixels that make up the picture</item>
<item>the ratio of the horizontal and vertical viewing areas of the monitor</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 13 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What type of connector can be used to connect
an internal hard drive to the motherboard?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>USB</item>
<item goed="ja">SATA</item>
<item>eSATA</item>
<item>Thunderbolt</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 14 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two factors must be considered when
replacing old RAM modules in a PC?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>The new RAM must be compatible with BIOS or UEFI.</item>
<item goed="ja">The new RAM must be compatible with the motherboard.</item>
<item goed="ja">The speed of the new RAM must be supported by the chipset.</item>
<item>The power supply must provide the voltage that is required by the new RAM.</item>
<item>The new RAM must match the old RAM in terms of capacity and speed.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 15 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which term is used to define the wires on a motherboard
that move data from one part of a computer to another?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">bus</item>
<item>I/O card</item>
<item>bridge</item>
<item>chipset</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 16 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
When a new PC is being built, which component has the most
influence when selecting the case and power supply?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>video card</item>
<item>sound card</item>
<item>RAM module</item>
<item goed="ja">motherboard</item>
<item>hard disk type</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 17 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the function of the power supply?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">to convert AC power into a lower voltage DC power</item>
<item>to convert AC power into a higher voltage DC power</item>
<item>to convert DC power into a lower voltage AC power</item>
<item>to convert DC power into a higher voltage AC power</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
De voeding is het component dat netstroom omzet naar voltages die
gebruikt worden door de componenten van de computer. Netspanning is
wisselspanning (Alternating Current), 230V in Europa en 110V in
Amerika. Vrijwel alle computeronderdelen maken gebruik van
gelijkspanning (Direct Current) op voltages zoals 12V, 5V en 3.3V.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 18 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two considerations would be of the greatest importance when building
a workstation that will run multiple virtual machines? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">amount of RAM</item>
<item goed="ja">number of CPU cores</item>
<item>water cooling</item>
<item>powerful video card</item>
<item>high-end sound card</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
Een systeem dat meerdere virtuele machines zal draaien zal voor elke
virtuele machine dezelfde hoeveelheid geheugen vereisen als een
vergelijkbare fysieke machine. Bij elkaar opgeteld zal het dus een
om een grote hoeveelheid vereist RAM geheugen gaan.
Er vanuitgaande dat de virtuele machines een gemiddelde hoeveelheid
rekenkracht vereisen, zullen er ook meer CPU cores nodig zijn om
een fatsoenlijke snelheid te kunnen halen.
Water koeling is niet gebruikelijk voor een workstation.
Videokaart en geluidskaart zijn compleet niet interessant voor
virtuele machines, vaak worden virtuele machines zelfs headless
gedraaid, waarbij er dus niet eens een videokaart of geluidskaart
gebruikt wordt.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 19 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user playing a game on a gaming PC with a standard EIDE 5400 RPM hard
drive finds the performance unsatisfactory. Which hard drive upgrade would
improve performance while providing more reliability and more energy
efficiency?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>a 7200 RPM EIDE hard drive</item>
<item>a 7200 RPM SATA hard drive</item>
<item>a 10,000 RPM SATA hard drive</item>
<item goed="ja">an SSD</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 20 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What three components should be included in a computer that is used to
create TV commercials and music videos? (Choose three.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>extra DIN-6 ports</item>
<item goed="ja">specialized video card</item>
<item>extra PS/2 ports</item>
<item goed="ja">large and fast hard drives</item>
<item>VGA adaptors</item>
<item goed="ja">specialized audio card</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 21 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What are two hardware requirements for computers that will be
used to run multiple virtual machines? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">large amounts of RAM</item>
<item goed="ja">a multicore CPU</item>
<item>a high resolution video card</item>
<item>a high speed wireless adapter</item>
<item>multiple monitors</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
Vrijwel dezelfde vraag als een paar vragen terug.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 22 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which memory technology allows two memory
modules to be accessed at the same time?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">dual channel</item>
<item>double-sided</item>
<item>SRAM</item>
<item>ECC</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
De naam zegt het feitelijk al. Met double-sided wordt waarschijnlijk
slechts bedoeld dat er aansluitingen aan beide kanten van de
module zitten. SRAM zegt niets over concurrency. ECC is een techniek
voor foutcontrole, wat in principe niet op consumentenelectronica zat.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 23 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which security feature in modern CPUs protects memory areas that
contain part of the operating system from malware attacks?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>encryption</item>
<item>TPM</item>
<item goed="ja">execute disable bit</item>
<item>LoJack</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 24 -->
<!--
<exercise>
<vraag>
Drag the description on left to its RAID level on the right.
</vraag>
<drag>
<left>
<item>highest performance</item>
<item>disk mirroring</item>
<item>combination of data striping and parity</item>
<item>data striping without redundancy</item>
<item>ability of data to be rebuilt with information from the other drives</item>
<item>high performance and high protection because all data is duplicated</item>
</left>
<right>
</right>
</drag>
</exercise>
-->

<!-- Vraag 25 -->
<!--
<exercise>
<vraag>
Match the ports or cables with their descriptions. (Not all options are used.)
</vraag>
</exercise>
-->

<!-- Vraag 1 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A new technician has joined the IT team and is about to service a heavy
printer. What advice would you give this technician to avoid any injury
when transporting the heavy printer to the service area?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
Bend your knees to use the strength in your legs to lift the printer.
</item>
<item>Avoid bending your knees when lifting the printer.</item>
<item>Bend your back to pick the printer up.</item>
<item>Use your arms and back to lift the printer.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 2 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
How does an inline UPS protect computer equipment
against electrical power brownouts and blackouts?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>by grounding excess electrical voltage</item>
<item goed="ja">by using a battery to supply a constant level of voltage</item>
<item>by switching from main power to a standby power source</item>
<item>by stopping the flow of voltage to the computer</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 3 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which circumstance increase the likelihood of ESD damage to a computer?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">working in low levels of humidity</item>
<item>using a magnetic screwdriver while working on a hard drive</item>
<item>plugging a printer into an UPS</item>
<item>self grounding against the computer case</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
Jezelf aarden tegen de computerkast zal juist helpen ESD te verminderen.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 4 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which condition refers to a reduced voltage level of
AC power that lasts for an extended period of time?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Brownout</item>
<item>Sag</item>
<item>Spike</item>
<item>Surge</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 5 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What are two significant sources of EMI? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>infrared mice</item>
<item>RAM modules</item>
<item goed="ja">electrical storms</item>
<item>LCD monitors</item>
<item goed="ja">power lines</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 6 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
A technician is unpacking a new PCIe video adapter from an antistatic
bag to install the card in a desktop computer. Which two measures should
the technician use to protect the card and other computer
components? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Use a grounded mat on the workbench.</item>
<item goed="ja">Use a correctly connected antistatic wrist strap.</item>
<item>Shield the card and computer from sources of EMI.</item>
<item>Ensure that the workplace has a low humidity environment.</item>
<item>Connect the computer to a UPS while installing the card.</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
Een lage luchtvochtigheid zal juist problemen met statische electriciteit
veroorzaken.
Een UPS voorziet een computer van stroom tijdens stroomuitval. Uiteraard hoeft
de computer niet aan te staan tijdens het plaatsen van componenten, dit is zelfs
af te raden, hoewel het voor componenten zoals een videokaart niet strikt
noodzakelijk is om de computer uit te zetten.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 7 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
How should a technician dispose of an empty inkjet printer cartridge?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Refill it.</item>
<item>Throw it away.</item>
<item goed="ja">Follow local regulations for disposal.</item>
<item>Give it back to the customer.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 8 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What makes CRT monitor disposal dangerous for
a technician who is handling the disposal?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>potential breathing hazards</item>
<item>potential explosive materials</item>
<item goed="ja">potential residual high voltage</item>
<item>potential health-damaging chemicals</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 9 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is troubleshooting connectivity issues to a PC and needs
to verify which cable is plugged into the correct port of the patch
panel. What tool should the technician use?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>multimeter</item>
<item goed="ja">toner probe</item>
<item>punch down</item>
<item>crimper</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 10 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which tool is designed to loosen or tighten crosshead screws?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">phillips screwdriver</item>
<item>hex driver</item>
<item>flat head screwdriver</item>
<item>torx driver</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 11 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What tool would a technician use to remove a slotted screw?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">flat head screwdriver</item>
<item>hex driver</item>
<item>needle-nosed pliers</item>
<item>Phillips head screwdriver</item>
<item>Torx screwdriver</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 12 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which tool in Windows OS gives a technician access
to initialize disks and create partitions?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Optimize Drives</item>
<item>Disk Cleanup</item>
<item goed="ja">Disk Management</item>
<item>Format</item>
<item>Scandisk</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
Disk Management kan gebruikt worden voor het partitioneren van schijven.
Format wordt gebruikt om partities te formatteren met een bestandssysteem.
Scandisk wordt gebruikt om een bestaand bestandssysteem te controleren
op fouten.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 13 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which Windows OS tool scans the critical files of the operating
system and replaces any files that have been corrupted?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Chkdsk</item>
<item>Defrag</item>
<item>Disk Cleanup</item>
<item>Disk Management</item>
<item>Scan System</item>
<item goed="ja">System File Checker</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
<p>
Chkdsk heeft een vergelijkbare functie als scandisk en wordt gebruikt om
een bestaand bestandssysteen te controleren op fouten.
</p>
<p>
Defrag wordt gebruikt om een bestaand bestandssysteem op volgorde te
zetten.
</p>
<p>
Disk Management kan gebruikt worden voor het partitioneren van schijven.
</p>
<p>
System File Checker is het juiste antwoord.
</p>
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 14 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which tool should be used if a user needs to optimize space on a hard drive?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Optimize Drives</item>
<item>Disk Management</item>
<item>Fdisk</item>
<item>Format</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 15 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Why is documentation of all services and repairs
an important organizational tool for a technician?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>It increases the cost of services and repairs.</item>
<item>It allows the public sharing of information on the Internet.</item>
<item>It reduces the technical skills required of new technicians.</item>
<item goed="ja">
It provides reference material for similar problems when
they are encountered in the future.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 16 -->
<!-- niet echt mee eens -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which tool could potentially cause data loss on hard disk or floppy drives?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">a magnetic screwdriver</item>
<item>compressed air</item>
<item>a lead pencil</item>
<item>a computer vacuum cleaner</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
Deze kans is echter klein.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 17 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Why should an antistatic wrist strap be worn when working on
electronic equipment?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>to prevent interference from clothing and loose jewelry</item>
<item goed="ja">to equalize the electrical charge between a person and the equipment</item>
<item>
to prevent clothing made of silk, polyester, or wool from generating a static charge
</item>
<item>
to draw static electricity away from a component and
transfer it safely from equipment to a grounding point
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 18 -->
<!-- niet mee eens -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which precaution should be taken when working inside computer systems?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Avoid using magnetized tools.</item>
<item>Leave the power cord attached to an outlet for grounding.</item>
<item>Wear ESD protection to repair monitors in humid environments.</item>
<item>Avoid using ESD wrist straps and ESD mats simultaneously.</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
ESD wrist straps en matten moeten juist wel gebruikt worden.
Het goede antwoord moet "Avoid using magnetized tools" zijn, maar dit
zal echter vrijwel nooit een probleem opleveren en bijna niemand
vermijd bewust gemagnetiseerde schroevendraaiers.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 19 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which cleaning solution is recommended to
clean the contacts of computer components?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>rubbing alcohol</item>
<item goed="ja">isopropyl alcohol</item>
<item>glass cleaner with ammonia</item>
<item>water that is mixed with a small amount of dishwashing liquid</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 20 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Why should a pencil never be used as a tool when working inside a computer?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Pencil lead is corrosive.</item>
<item goed="ja">Pencil lead is conductive</item>
<item>A pencil can hold a static charge.</item>
<item>The lead in a pencil can induce current.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 21 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician suspects that a power supply is faulty. How can it be checked?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>by checking the temperature of the power supply</item>
<item goed="ja">by using a multimeter</item>
<item>by taking apart the power supply</item>
<item>by powering up the PC after disconnecting each connector in turn</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 22 -->
<!--
<exercise type="lines">
<vraag>
Match the steps of fire extinguisher operation to the order in which they
should be completed. (Not all options are used.)
</vraag>
</exercise>
-->

<!-- Vraag 1 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
When a computer is being assembled, which action can be taken
to help eliminate cable clutter within a computer case?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Install a CPU without using a heat sink and fan assembly.</item>
<item>Install a 2.5in HDD instead of a 3.5in HDD.</item>
<item goed="ja">Install a modular power supply.</item>
<item>Install a motherboard without using standoffs in the case.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 2 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the best way to apply thermal compound when reseating a CPU?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
Clean the CPU and the base of the heat sink with
isopropyl alcohol before applying the thermal compound.
</item>
<item>
Use rubbing alcohol to clean the base of the
heat sink before applying thermal compound.
</item>
<item>
Scrape off the old thermal compound on the heat sink
with a sharp knife and apply the thermal compound liberally.
</item>
<item>
Put a thick layer of thermal compound over the
existing thermal compound before reseating the CPU.
</item>
<item>
Change the base of the heat sink before applying the thermal compound.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 3 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is installing additional memory in a computer. How can
the technician guarantee that the memory is correctly aligned?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>The label on the memory module should always face the CPU.</item>
<item goed="ja">
A notch in the memory module should be
aligned with a notch in the memory slot.
</item>
<item>
The arrows on the memory module should be
aligned with the arrows on the motherboard slot.
</item>
<item>Memory slots are color coded, with one end red and one end blue.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 4 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is used to prevent the motherboard from
touching metal portions of the computer case?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>an I/O shield</item>
<item>thermal compound</item>
<item goed="ja">standoffs</item>
<item>ZIF sockets</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 5 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which statement describes the purpose of an I/O connector plate?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
It makes the I/O ports of the motherboard available
for connection in a variety of computer cases.
</item>
<item>
It plugs into the motherboard and expands the
number of available slots for adapter cards.
</item>
<item>
It provides multiple connections for SATA
hard drives to connect to the motherboard.
</item>
<item>
It connects the PCIe adapter slots used for
video directly to the CPU for faster processing.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 6 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What are three important considerations when
installing a CPU on a motherboard? (Choose three.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Antistatic precautions are taken.</item>
<item goed="ja">The CPU is correctly aligned and placed in the socket.</item>
<item>The CPU contacts are first cleaned with isopropyl alcohol.</item>
<item goed="ja">The CPU heat sink and fan assembly are correctly installed.</item>
<item>The CMOS EPROM battery is removed prior to installing the CPU.</item>
<item>
Maximum insertion force is applied to the load lever so the CPU is locked in place.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 7 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which type of drive is typically installed in a 5.25 inch (13.34 cm) bay?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>hard drive</item>
<item goed="ja">optical drive</item>
<item>flash drive</item>
<item>SSD</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 8 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which type of motherboard expansion slot has four types ranging from x1 to x16
with each type having a different length of expansion slot?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">PCIe</item>
<item>AGP</item>
<item>SATA</item>
<item>PCI</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 9 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is installing a new high-end video adapter card into an expansion
slot on a motherboard. What may be needed to operate this video adapter card?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>PCI expansion slot</item>
<item>PCIe x8 expansion slot</item>
<item goed="ja">Two 8-pin power connectors</item>
<item>24-pin ATX power connector</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 10 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
When assembling a PC, how is pin 1 identified on the front panel cables so that it
can be aligned properly with pin 1 on the motherboard panel connector?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">by a small arrow or notch</item>
<item>by a plus sign</item>
<item>by a P1</item>
<item>by a red cable</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 11 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician has just finished assembling a new computer. When the computer is
powered up for the first time, the POST discovers a problem. How does the POST
indicate the error?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">It issues a number of short beeps.</item>
<item>The LED on the front of the computer case flashes a number of times.</item>
<item>It places an error message in the BIOS.</item>
<item>It locks the keyboard.</item>
</choice>
<tags>
<tag>LED</tag>
<tag>BIOS</tag>
<tag>POST</tag>
</tags>
<toelichting>
Het BIOS zal bij de detectie van een fout tijdens de POST uiteraard een
bericht op het beeldscherm weergeven, maar omdat er niet vanuit gegaan
kan worden dat het graficshe gedeelte van de computer functioneel is, zal
er ook een foutmelding gegeven worden in de vorm van pieptonen uit de
PC-speaker. De gebruiker moet dan opzoeken wat een betreffend pieptoon
patroon betekent.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 12 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is a function of the BIOS?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>enables a computer to connect to a network</item>
<item>provides temporary data storage for the CPU</item>
<item goed="ja">performs a check on all internal components</item>
<item>provides graphic capabilities for games and applications</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 13 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician has assembled a new computer and must now configure the BIOS. At
which point must a key be pressed to start the BIOS setup program?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>before the computer is powered on</item>
<item>during the Windows load process</item>
<item goed="ja">during the POST</item>
<item>after the POST, but before Windows starts to load</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 14 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What data is stored in the CMOS memory chip?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">BIOS settings</item>
<item>Windows configuration settings</item>
<item>user login information</item>
<item>device drivers</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 15 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the purpose of LoJack?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
It allows the owner of a device to remotely
locate, lock, or delete all files from the device.
</item>
<item>
It ensures that a computer will only boot an operating
system that is trusted by the motherboard manufacturer.
</item>
<item>
It provides passwords for different levels of access to the BIOS.
</item>
<item>
It encrypts data on hard drives to prevent access without the correct password.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 16 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which is a BIOS security feature that can prevent data from being read from a
hard drive even if the hard drive is moved to another computer?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">drive encryption</item>
<item>RAID</item>
<item>secure boot</item>
<item>BIOS passwords</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 17 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is one purpose of adjusting the clock speed within the BIOS configuration
settings?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
to allow a computer to run multiple operating systems in files or partitions
</item>
<item>to change the order of the bootable partitions</item>
<item>to disable devices that are not needed or used by the computer</item>
<item goed="ja">to allow the computer to run slower and cooler</item>
</choice>
<tags>
<tag>clock speed</tag>
<tag>BIOS</tag>
</tags>
<toelichting>
<p>
meerdere besturingssystemen, de volgorde van bootable partities en
het uitschakelen van apparaten hebben niks met kloksnelheid te maken.
</p>
<p>
Het is wel mogelijk om de computer (met name de CPU) sneller of langzamer
te laten draaien door de kloksnelheid van de Front Side Bus aan te passen.
Er moet wel rekening mee gehouden worden dat de kloksnelheid van het RAM
geheugen ook afgeleid is van de Front Side Bus, deze zal dus ook
veranderen. Ook moet voor een hogere kloksnelheid van de CPU de Vcore
spanning van de CPU hoger zijn, wat meer stroomverbruik en hitte zal
betekenen. Voor een lagere snelheid kan je uiteraard af met een
lagere Vcore spanning waardoor de processor inderdaad koeler zal blijven.
</p>
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 18 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
A technician is assembling a new computer. Which two components are often
easier to install before mounting the motherboard in the case? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">CPU</item>
<item goed="ja">memory</item>
<item>NIC</item>
<item>sound card</item>
<item>video card</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 19 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two components are commonly replaced when a computer system with a
newer motherboard is being upgraded? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">RAM</item>
<item>hard disk drive</item>
<item goed="ja">CPU</item>
<item>optical drive</item>
<item>CMOS battery</item>
<item>adapter card</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 20 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user reports that every morning when a particular computer is turned on, the
configuration settings on that computer have to be reset. What action should be
taken to remedy this situation?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Replace the motherboard.</item>
<item goed="ja">Replace the CMOS battery.</item>
<item>Move the jumpers,</item>
<item>Upgrade the BIOS</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 21 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What are two reasons for installing a second hard disk drive inside an existing
computer? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">to support a RAID array</item>
<item>to store BIOS configuration settings</item>
<item goed="ja">to store a system swap file</item>
<item>to increase CPU speed</item>
<item>to allow access to a secondary display output</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 22 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
When should a technician use unsigned drivers for newly installed computer
hardware?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>if the unsigned driver is the most current driver available</item>
<item>if the original installation media is not available</item>
<item goed="ja">
if the source of the drivers is trusted by the technician
</item>
<item>
if the Windows installation media does not contain a valid signed driver
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 23 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What computer component is often required to allow a single computer to use two
monitors simultaneously?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>an extra power supply</item>
<item goed="ja">a second video adapter card</item>
<item>an extra USB connection</item>
<item>a KVM switch</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 24 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician notices that half of the memory slots on a motherboard are colored
differently from the other half. Which technology is probably implemented on this
system?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>virtualization</item>
<item>ECC</item>
<item goed="ja">double channeling</item>
<item>double-sided</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 1 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which negative environmental factor does cleaning the inside of a computer
reduce?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">dust</item>
<item>EMI</item>
<item>rust</item>
<item>ESD</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 2 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which component can be easily damaged by the direct spray of compressed air
when cleaning the inside the computer case?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">fan</item>
<item>heat sink</item>
<item>power supply</item>
<item>CPU</item>
<item>cable connectors</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 3 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
On the production floor, a furniture plant has laptops for process monitoring and
reporting. The production floor environment is around 80 degrees Fahrenheit (27
degrees Celsius). The humidity level is fairly high around 70 percent. Fans are
mounted in the ceiling for air circulation. Wood dust is prevalent. Which condition
is most likely to adversely affect a laptop that is used in this environment?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>the temperature</item>
<item>the humidity</item>
<item>the air flow</item>
<item goed="ja">the dust</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 4 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A vegetable canning plant uses laptops for monitoring of assembly lines. The
production environment has an ambient temperature around 75 degrees
Fahrenheit (24 degrees Celsius). The humidity level is around 30 percent. Noise
levels are high due to the canning machinery. The laptops are in a wooden box
that tightly surrounds the laptop on three sides. Which factor is most likely to
adversely affect a laptop that is used in this environment?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>the room temperature</item>
<item>the humidity</item>
<item>the noise</item>
<item goed="ja">the laptop container</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 5 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A scientific expedition team is using laptops for their work. The temperatures
where the scientists are working range from -13 degrees Fahrenheit (-25 degree
Celsius) to 80 degrees Fahrenheit (27 degrees Celsius). The humidity level is
around 40 percent. Noise levels are low, but the terrain is rough and winds can
reach 45 miles per hour (72 kilometers per hour). When needed, the scientists
stop walking and enter the data using the laptop. Which condition is most likely to
adversely affect a laptop that is used in this environment?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">the temperature</item>
<item>the humidity</item>
<item>the rough terrain</item>
<item>the wind</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 6 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is part of creating a preventive maintenance plan?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
documenting the details and frequency of each maintenance task
</item>
<item>performing hardware upgrades</item>
<item>discarding all replaced parts</item>
<item>performing a forensic audit of security breaches</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 7 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is performing hardware maintenance of PCs at a construction site.
What task should the technician perform as part of a preventive maintenance
plan?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Remove dust from intake fans.</item>
<item>Back up the data, reformat the hard drive, and reinstall the data.</item>
<item>Develop and install forensic tracking software.</item>
<item>Perform an audit of all software that is installed.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 8 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which task should be part of a hardware maintenance routine?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Review security updates.</item>
<item>Update virus definition files.</item>
<item>Adjust the monitor for optimum resolution.</item>
<item>Remove dust from inside the hard drive.</item>
<item goed="ja">Check for and secure any loose cables.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 9 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
During the process of testing a theory of several probable causes to a problem,
which should be tested first?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">the easiest and most obvious</item>
<item>those the customer believes to be the most important</item>
<item>the most complex and difficult to diagnose</item>
<item>those chosen by random selection</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 10 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two items could be used to help establish a plan of action when resolving a
computer problem? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>a multimeter</item>
<item>a loopback plug</item>
<item goed="ja">the computer manual</item>
<item goed="ja">the computer repair history log</item>
<item>BIOS diagnostics</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 11 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two types of data should be backed up before troubleshooting a computer
for a customer? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>BIOS system file</item>
<item>driver files for the hard disk</item>
<item goed="ja">Internet Explorer favorites files</item>
<item>Windows operating system files</item>
<item goed="ja">documents that are created by the customer</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 12 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A customer reports that recently several files cannot be accessed. The service
technician decides to check the hard disk status and the file system structure. The
technician asks the customer if a backup has been performed on the disk and the
customer replies that the backup was done a week ago to a different logical
partition on the disk. What should the technician do before performing diagnostic
procedures on the disk?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Run the CHKDSK utility.</item>
<item goed="ja">Back up the user data to a removable drive.</item>
<item>Perform file restore from the existing backup copy at the logical partition.</item>
<item>Install a new hard disk as the primary disk, then make the current disk a slave.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 13 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the next step after a possible solution is implemented during a
troubleshooting process?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Test another possible solution.</item>
<item>Identify other possible causes for the problem.</item>
<item>Document the cause and the solution for the problem.</item>
<item goed="ja">
Verify the full system functionality and apply maintenance procedures.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 14 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
An employee reports that the antivirus software cannot obtain updates. The
support technician notices that the license for the software has expired. The
technician adds a new license to the software and completes the update service.
What should the technician do next?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Record the new license number in the log.</item>
<item>Download advanced antivirus software from another vendor.</item>
<item goed="ja">Run a full virus scan on the computer.</item>
<item>
Review the Event Viewer for the date and time that the last software update was
performed.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 15 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What task should be completed before escalating a problem to a higher-level
technician?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Document each test that was tried.</item>
<item>Ask the customer to open a new support request.</item>
<item>Redo each test to ensure the accuracy of the results.</item>
<item>Replace all hardware components with components that are known to work.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 16 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which step of the six-step troubleshooting process is where a technician would
ask the computer user to print a document on a newly installed printer?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Test the theory to determine the cause.</item>
<item>Identify the problem.</item>
<item>Establish a theory of probable cause.</item>
<item>Document findings, actions, and outcomes.</item>
<item>
Establish a plan of action to resolve the problem and implement the solution.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
Verify full system functionality and, if applicable, implement preventive measures.
</item>
</choice>
<tags>
<tag>printer</tag>
</tags>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 17 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
After a technician tests a theory of probable causes, what two actions should the
technician take if the testing did not identify an exact cause? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Establish a new theory of probable causes.</item>
<item>Randomly replace components one at a time until the problem is solved.</item>
<item goed="ja">Document each test tried that did not correct the problem.</item>
<item>Verify full system functionality.</item>
<item>Test all remaining possible causes starting with the most complex.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 18 -->
<!-- Opmerking -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the preferred method to remove a disc from an optical drive that fails to
eject the disc?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
Insert a pin into the small hole on the front of the drive.</item>
<item>Use a small screwdriver and pry the drive door open.</item>
<item>Remove the top of the drive enclosure.</item>
<item>Send the drive to an authorized repair depot.
</item>
</choice>
<tags>
<tag>optical drive</tag>
</tags>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 19 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is called to an office where the computer is randomly rebooting.
Which of the given components would most likely cause this issue?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>BIOS</item>
<item>CMOS battery</item>
<item>optical drive</item>
<item goed="ja">power supply</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 20 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What would happen if a PC that contains a power supply that does not
automatically adjust for input voltage is set to 230 volts and attaches to an outlet
in the United States?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>The power supply would explode.</item>
<item goed="ja">The PC would not turn on.</item>
<item>The PC would display an error code.</item>
<item>The PC would emit a series of beeps.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 21 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
During the troubleshooting of a PC that will not boot, it is suspected that the
problem is with the RAM modules. The RAM modules are removed and put into
another PC, which successfully powers on. The RAM modules are then put back
into the original PC and it now successfully powers on as well. What was the most
likely cause of the problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>The RAM modules have bad blocks.</item>
<item goed="ja">The RAM modules were not seated firmly.</item>
<item>The RAM modules did not match the PC specs.</item>
<item>The RAM modules were inserted backwards into the DIMM slots.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 22 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
After a new PCIe video card is added, the computer seems to boot successfully
but it will not display any video. The computer was working properly before the
new video card was installed. What is the most likely cause of the problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>The monitor cable is faulty.</item>
<item>The new video card is not compatible with the CPU in the PC.</item>
<item goed="ja">
The saved CMOS settings are set to use the built-in video adapter.
</item>
<item>The PC does not have enough RAM to support the new video card.</item>
</choice>
<tags>
<tag>PCIe</tag>
<tag>video</tag>
<tag>CMOS</tag>
</tags>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 23 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user has opened a ticket that indicates that the computer clock keeps losing the
correct time. What is the most likely cause of the problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>The motherboard clocking crystal is damaged.</item>
<item>The operating system needs to be patched.</item>
<item goed="ja">The CMOS battery is loose or failing.</item>
<item>The CPU needs to be overclocked.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 24 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
An employee reports that each time a workstation is started it locks up after about
5 minutes of use. What is the most likely cause of the problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>The hard disk is failing.</item>
<item>The RAM is malfunctioning.</item>
<item goed="ja">The CPU is overheating.</item>
<item>The power supply fails to provide adequate voltage and current.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 25 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user reports that images on a computer display are distorted. The technician
sends an intern to look at the problem. What could the technician tell the intern to
check first that does not involve hardware replacement or disassembly?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>LCD backlight adjustment</item>
<item goed="ja">display settings</item>
<item>work desk stability</item>
<item>electrical interference</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 26 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user has connected an external monitor to a laptop VGA port. What is the next
step the user should take?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Disable the current display being used by the laptop.</item>
<item>Access the BIOS and enable the VGA port on the laptop.</item>
<item>
Reboot the system so that the currently connected external display can be recognized
by the laptop.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
Use a Fn key along with a multi-purpose key to send video to the external display.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 1 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What are two functions of an operating system? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">controlling hardware access</item>
<item goed="ja">managing applications</item>
<item>text processing</item>
<item>flow chart editing</item>
<item>program compilation</item>
<item>web browsing</item>
<item>controlling the BIOS</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 2 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two methods should a technician use
to update a device driver? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
Insert the operating system installation media and load the driver from there.
</item>
<item goed="ja">Use the media that came with the device.</item>
<item>Buy another operating system license.</item>
<item goed="ja">
Download the driver from the website of the manufacturer.
</item>
<item>Perform a firmware update.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 3 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the term for the ability of a computer
to run multiple applications at the same time?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>multiuser</item>
<item goed="ja">multitasking</item>
<item>multimedia</item>
<item>multiprocessing</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 4 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is provided by an operating system
that has multiprocessing capability?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">support for two or more processors</item>
<item>support for two or more users</item>
<item>the capability to run multiple applications at the same time</item>
<item>the ability to run different parts of a program at the same time</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 5 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is used by an operating system to communicate with hardware components?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">device driver</item>
<item>BIOS</item>
<item>CMOS</item>
<item>Application Program Interface</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 6 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which application interface is comprised of multiple APIs
that support multimedia tasks in Windows operating systems?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">DirectX</item>
<item>Java</item>
<item>Windows API</item>
<item>OpenGL</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 7 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which version of Windows introduced the Metro user interface, which
can be used on desktops, laptops, mobile phones, and tablets?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Windows XP</item>
<item>Windows Vista</item>
<item>Windows 7</item>
<item goed="ja">Windows 8</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 8 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Where can a technician look to determine if specific computer
hardware or software has been tested to work with Windows 7?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Microsoft Compatibility Center</item>
<item>Microsoft Knowledge Base</item>
<item>Windows 7 manual</item>
<item>Windows Easy Transfer</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 9 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is critical to consider when determining the version of Windows to install on
a desktop computer?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>version of Microsoft Office installed</item>
<item>type of monitor installed</item>
<item>off-the-shelf applications installed</item>
<item goed="ja">customized applications installed</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 10 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user downloads and uses the Windows 7 Upgrade Advisor to generate a report
on a PC that is being considered for an operating system upgrade. What
information would the report contain?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">recommended changes to hardware</item>
<item>recommended changes to file systems</item>
<item>recommended changes to user permissions</item>
<item>recommended changes to directory structures</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 11 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What are two features of the active partition
of a hard drive that is using MBR? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">The active partition must be a primary partition.</item>
<item>Up to four primary partitions can be marked as active.</item>
<item>An active partition must be assigned C: as the drive letter.</item>
<item goed="ja">
The operating system uses the active partition to boot the system.</item>
<item>
The active partition may include the manufacturer recovery partition.
</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
Met de MBR partitie methode kunnen vier primaire partities aangemaakt
worden. Het is de bedoeling een van de vier primaire partities als
actief te markeren. In de regel zal bij het opstarten dan het
bootrecord van deze actieve partitie uitgevoerd worden om de
computer op te starten. Wanneer
toch meerdere partities als actief gemarkeerd zijn, zal de eerste van
deze gekozen worden.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 12 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A computer with the Windows 7 operating system fails to boot when the system is
powered on. The technician suspects that the operating system has been attacked
by a virus that rendered the system inoperable. What measure could be taken to
restore system functionality?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Use a differential backup to restore the system.</item>
<item>Use an incremental backup to restore the system.</item>
<item goed="ja">
Use a system image that was created prior
to the failure to restore the system.
</item>
<item>
Run chkdsk on the affected drive to restore
system files to their post-installation state.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 13 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>What is the purpose of a recovery partition?</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
to provide a copy of the C: partition and
data from the last backup in case of failure
</item>
<item>to provide a backup copy of the BIOS</item>
<item>
to return the system to an earlier state to recover from a failed update
</item>
<item>
to restore the computer to the factory state without deleting user files
</item>
<item goed="ja">to restore the computer to its factory state</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 14 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What Windows 8 tool allows the computer to be rolled back to its factory state
without losing any user files?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>recovery partition</item>
<item>System Restore</item>
<item goed="ja">Refresh your PC</item>
<item>BIOS backup</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 15 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A Windows 8 computer locks up with a stop error during startup and then
automatically reboots. The automatic restart setting is making it difficult to see
any error messages. What can be done so that the error messages can be
viewed?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
Use the System Recovery options to restart the operating system.
</item>
<item>
Use the Command Prompt option to research the stop error messages.
</item>
<item>
View the error messages and recover the
system using the System Image Recovery tool.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
Access the Advanced Startup options menu before the
OS loads to disable the auto restart function.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 16 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user installs a new video driver on a computer that was working properly. After
the new driver is installed and the computer is restarted, the computer fails to
boot. How can the user quickly return the computer to a working state?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
Restart the PC with the Windows System Recovery
disc and use the Startup Repair utility.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
Press F8 while the computer is booting and choose
the Last Known Good Configuration option.
</item>
<item>
Boot the system with the original Windows installation
media and choose the Repair Your Computer option.
</item>
<item>
Press F8 while the computer is booting and
choose the Start Windows Normally option.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 17 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Where are the settings that are chosen
during the installation process stored?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>in the recovery partition</item>
<item>in BIOS</item>
<item>in flash memory</item>
<item goed="ja">in the Registry</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 18 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Why is it important to register a DLL file in Windows?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
so that any program needing to use that
specific program code can locate the file
</item>
<item>
so that the operating system can be restored
</item>
<item>
so that the computer can be restored to factory settings
</item>
<item>
so that copyright laws are not violated when computer images are made
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 19 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A Windows 8.1 system is unable to boot properly. What
is the procedure to boot this system into Safe Mode?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
From the command prompt run the shutdown -r -s command.
</item>
<item>
Run the MSCONFIG utility and choose the option Selective Startup.
</item>
<item>
Reboot the system and press Del or F2 depending on the system.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
Reboot the system, press and hold F8 until a
menu is displayed, and then choose Safe Mode.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 20 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician has installed a new video driver on a Windows 8.1 computer and now
the monitor shows distorted images. The technician needs to install a different
video driver that is available on a network server. What startup mode should the
technician use to access the driver on the network?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Safe Mode</item>
<item>Safe Mode with Networking</item>
<item>Debugging Mode</item>
<item>Safe mode with Command Prompt</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 21 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is considering implementing RAID 5 before
installing Windows. Which technology does RAID 5 use?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>spanning</item>
<item>mirroring</item>
<item goed="ja">striping with parity</item>
<item>lazy write</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 22 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is a characteristic of a spanned volume?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
Data is stored across two or more disks for faster read and write access.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
Data is seen as one volume, but is stored across two or more disks.</item>
<item>A copy of one disk is placed on another disk for fault tolerance.</item>
<item>
Data is striped across a total of three or more disks, but one
disk is used for parity in order to provide fault tolerance.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 23 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which Windows tool is used to determine if a dynamic disk is corrupted?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Disk Management</item>
<item>Device Manager</item>
<item>Microsoft System Preparation</item>
<item>Bootmgr</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 24 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user has upgraded a PC to Windows 7 but still needs to use an application that
is created for the earlier version of Windows. Which mode of operation within
Windows 7 can be used to run the application?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>real mode</item>
<item>protected mode</item>
<item>virtual mode</item>
<item goed="ja">compatibility mode</item>
<item>multiuser mode</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 25 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Within which folder would a user of 64-bit Windows 8 find 32-bit programs?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>C:\Program Files</item>
<item goed="ja">C:\Program Files (x86)</item>
<item>C:\Program Files (x64)</item>
<item>C:\Program Files (x32)</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 1 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What would be a reason for a computer user to use the Task Manager
Performance tab?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>to increase the performance of the CPU</item>
<item>to view the processes that are running and end a process if needed</item>
<item>to view the services that are currently running on the PC</item>
<item goed="ja">to check the CPU usage of the PC</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 2 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which feature in Windows 7 and 8 allows a user to temporarily view the desktop
that is behind open windows by moving the mouse over the right edge of the
taskbar?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Peek</item>
<item>Snap</item>
<item>Shake</item>
<item>Search</item>
<item>jump lists</item>
<item>thumbnail previews</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 3 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the minimum amount of RAM and hard drive space required to install 64-
bit Windows 8 on a PC?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>1 GB RAM and 10 GB hard disk space</item>
<item>1 GB RAM and 16 GB hard disk space</item>
<item>2 GB RAM and 16 GB hard disk space</item>
<item goed="ja">2 GB RAM and 20 GB hard disk space</item>
<item>4 GB RAM and 16 GB hard disk space</item>
<item>4 GB RAM and 20 GB hard disk space</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 4 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
After upgrading a computer to Windows 7, a user notices that the UAC (User
Account Control) panel appears more frequently. How can the user reduce the
frequency with which the UAC appears?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Reinstall all user programs in Compatibility Mode.</item>
<item>
Replace the graphics card with one that meets the
minimum hardware requirements for Windows 7.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
Lower the UAC setting in the Change User Account Control
settings dialog box of the User Accounts control panel.
</item>
<item>
In the Performance Options dialog box of the Performance Information
and Tools control panel, choose Adjust for Best Performance.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 5 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which Windows utility allows Windows 7 and 8 users
to quickly and easily share files and folders?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">HomeGroup</item>
<item>Action Center</item>
<item>Services</item>
<item>Device Manager</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 6 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which Windows administrative tool displays the usage of a number of computer
resources simultaneously and can help a technician decide if an upgrade is
needed?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Services</item>
<item>Event Viewer</item>
<item>Component Services</item>
<item goed="ja">Performance Monitor</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 7 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which type of startup must be selected for a service
that should run each time the computer is booted?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">automatic</item>
<item>boot</item>
<item>manual</item>
<item>start</item>
<item>startup</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 8 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which Windows tool allows an administrator to organize computer management
tools in one location for convenient use?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Task Scheduler</item>
<item>Services console</item>
<item>Performance Monitor console</item>
<item goed="ja">Microsoft Management console</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 9 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
To which category of hypervisor does the Microsoft Virtual PC belong?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Type 1</item>
<item goed="ja">Type 2</item>
<item>Type 3</item>
<item>Type 4</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 10 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What are two advantages of using PC virtualization? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>It protects the host machine from viruses attacks.</item>
<item goed="ja">
It allows multiple operating systems to run on a single PC simultaneously.
</item>
<item>It boosts the performance of the host machine through virtualization.</item>
<item goed="ja">It can provide cost savings.</item>
<item>It allows network threat identification.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 11 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A college uses virtualization technology to deploy information security courses.
Some of the lab exercises involve studying the characteristics of computer
viruses and worms. What is an advantage of conducting the lab exercises inside
the virtualized environment as opposed to using actual PCs?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
The lab exercises are performed faster inside of the virtualized environment.</item>
<item>
The virtualization environment has better tools to develop mitigation solutions.</item>
<item goed="ja">
Virus and worm attacks are more easily controlled in a virtualized environment, thus
helping to protect the college network and its devices from attack.
</item>
<item>
The viruses and worms will have limited functionality inside the virtualized environment.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 12 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
A software engineer is involved in the development of an application. For usability
tests, the engineer needs to make sure that the application will work in both
Windows 7 and Windows 8 environments. The features and functions must be
verified in the actual OS environment. The engineer is using a Windows 7
workstation. What two technologies can help the engineer achieve the usability
tests? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">dual boot</item>
<item>two separate CPUs</item>
<item>storage redundancy</item>
<item goed="ja">client-side virtualization</item>
<item>two separate hard disks</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 13 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician needs to use an application that is not supported by Windows
operating systems on the PC. How can the technician make this application run
on the PC?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Use the Windows Compatibility mode.</item>
<item>Install the application with elevated permissions as administrator.</item>
<item goed="ja">
Create a virtual machine with an operating system that supports the application.
</item>
<item>Install the application in safe mode.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 14 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What preventive maintenance action should be taken to help improve system
security?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Automate any antivirus scanners.</item>
<item>Defragment the hard drive.</item>
<item>Perform backups regularly.</item>
<item>Error check the hard drive.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 15 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which Windows 7 feature would an administrator use to configure a computer to
delete temporary files from the hard drive at 3:00 AM each day?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Disk Cleanup</item>
<item goed="ja">Task Scheduler</item>
<item>Device Manager</item>
<item>Computer Management</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 16 -->
<exercise>
<vraag type="single">
Which command is used from the Windows command prompt to schedule a
program to run at a specific time?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">AT</item>
<item>CMD</item>
<item>TASKLIST</item>
<item>TASKKILL</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 17 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
When troubleshooting a printer problem, a technician finds that the operating
system was automatically updated with a corrupt device driver. Which solution
would resolve this issue?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Roll back the driver.</item>
<item>Restart both the computer and the printer.</item>
<item>Scan the downloaded driver file with a virus scanner.</item>
<item>Upload the correct driver to the printer.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 18 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two Windows utilities can be used to help maintain hard disks on
computers that have had long periods of normal use? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item type="multi">Disk Cleanup</item>
<item>Disk Maintenance</item>
<item type="mutli">Disk Defragmenter</item>
<item>Disk Partition</item>
<item>Disk Format</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 19 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is a common step that a technician can take to determine the cause of an
operating system problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
Boot into Safe Mode to determine if the problem is driver related.
</item>
<item>Test the power supply.</item>
<item>Document the time spent to resolve the problem.</item>
<item>Check the fan connections and ensure the fan is working properly.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 20 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which question is an open ended question that could be used when helping a
customer troubleshoot a Windows problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Can you boot the operating system?</item>
<item>Have you changed your password recently?</item>
<item>Do you get a login prompt when the computer boots?</item>
<item goed="ja">What programs have you installed recently?</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 21 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user reports that logging into the workstation fails after a display driver has
been updated. The user insists that the password is typed in correctly. What is the
most likely cause of the problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>The password has changed.</item>
<item goed="ja">The Caps Lock key is set to on.</item>
<item>A display driver update failed.</item>
<item>The display setting has changed after a driver update.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 22 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user reports that a video editing program does not work properly after a sound
mixing program is installed. The technician suspects that a compatibility issue
might be the cause of the problem. What should the technician do to verify this
theory?"
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Update Windows OS.</item>
<item>Update the video editing software.</item>
<item goed="ja">Uninstall the sound mixing software.</item>
<item>Check if an update of the sound mixing software is available.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 23 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
A user reports to a technician that his computer freezes without any error
messages. What are two probable causes? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">An update has corrupted the operating system.</item>
<item>A process is not using enough system resources.</item>
<item goed="ja">The power supply is failing.</item>
<item>The MBR is corrupted.</item>
<item>The boot order is not set correctly in BIOS.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 24 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is trying to fix a Windows 7 computer that displays an Invalid Boot
Disk error after POST. What is a possible cause of the error?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>The boot.ini file is corrupt.</item>
<item>The ntldr.exe file is corrupt.</item>
<item>The ntdetect.com file is corrupt.</item>
<item goed="ja">The boot order is not set correctly in the BIOS.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Hoofdstuk 7 -->
<!-- Vraag 1 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
How many devices can a Bluetooth device connect to simultaneously?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>127</item>
<item goed="ja">7</item>
<item>10</item>
<item>24</item>
<item>5</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 2 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A device has an IPv6 address of 2001:0DB8:75a3:0214:0607:1234:aa10:ba01 /64.
What is the host identifier of the device?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>2001:0DB8:75a3</item>
<item goed="ja">0607:1234:aa10:ba01</item>
<item>2001:0DB8</item>
<item>ba01</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 3 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which layer of the OSI model is responsible for logical addressing and routing?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>application</item>
<item>data link</item>
<item>network</item>
<item>transport</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 4 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
When would a printer be considered a network host?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">when it is connected to a switch</item>
<item>when it is connected to a workstation</item>
<item>when it is connected to a laptop</item>
<item>when it is connected to a PC</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 5 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which device provides wireless connectivity to users as its primary function?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>switch</item>
<item>router</item>
<item goed="ja">access point</item>
<item>modem</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 6 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which technology is most often used to connect devices to a PAN?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>coaxial cabling</item>
<item goed="ja">Bluetooth</item>
<item>fiber optic cabling</item>
<item>IEEE 802.11n wireless</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 7 -->
<exercise>
<vraag>
Which three factors are reasons for a company to choose a client/server
model for a network instead of peer-to-peer? (Choose three.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
The network is small with fewer than eight users.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
The company network requires secure access to confidential information.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
The users need a central database to store inventory and sales information.
</item>
<item>
Each user understands how to safely share files across a network.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
The data gathered by the employees is critical
and should be backed up on a regular basis.
</item>
<item>
All employees passed a strict background check
as part of the corporate hiring practices.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 8 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>What is a characteristic of a WAN?</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
It connects multiple networks that are geographically separated.
</item>
<item>
It spans across a campus or city to enable sharing of regional resources.
</item>
<item>
It is typically owned and managed by a single home or business.
</item>
<item>
It requires a wireless access point to connect users to the network.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 9 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which three layers of the OSI model map to the application layer of the TCP/IP
model? (Choose three.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">application</item>
<item goed="ja">presentation</item>
<item goed="ja">session</item>
<item>transport</item>
<item>network</item>
<item>data link</item>
<item>physical</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 10 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the correct order of the layers of the
TCP/IP model from the top layer to the bottom?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>application, session, network, data link, physical</item>
<item>application, internet, network access, transport</item>
<item>network access, transport, internet, application</item>
<item goed="ja">application, transport, internet, network access</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 11 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What TCP/IP model layer is responsible for MAC addressing?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">network access</item>
<item>internet</item>
<item>transport</item>
<item>application</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 12 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What PDU is associated with the network layer of the OSI model?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>data</item>
<item>frame</item>
<item goed="ja">packet</item>
<item>segment</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 13 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two layers of the OSI model correspond to the functions
of the TCP/IP model network access layer? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">physical</item>
<item goed="ja">data link</item>
<item>network</item>
<item>transport</item>
<item>session</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 14 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is identified by the 100 in the 100BASE-TX standard?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">the maximum bandwidth in Mb/s</item>
<item>the maximum cable distance in meters</item>
<item>the maximum number of network nodes</item>
<item>o the series number of the standard</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 15 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two characteristics describe Ethernet technology? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">It is supported by IEEE 802.3 standards.</item>
<item>It is supported by IEEE 802.5 standards.</item>
<item>It typically uses an average of 16 Mb/s for data transfer rates.</item>
<item goed="ja">It uses the CSMA/CD access control method.</item>
<item>It uses a ring topology.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 16 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which IEEE standard operates at wireless frequencies
in both the 5 GHz and 2.4 GHz ranges?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">802.11n</item>
<item>802.11g</item>
<item>802.11b</item>
<item>802.11a</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 17 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
A customer is considering a multipurpose device to create a home network.
Which three devices are usually integrated into a multipurpose network device?
(Choose three.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>web server</item>
<item goed="ja">switch</item>
<item goed="ja">router</item>
<item>email server</item>
<item goed="ja">wireless access point</item>
<item>print server</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 18 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which network device makes forwarding decisions based on
the destination MAC address that is contained in the frame?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>repeater</item>
<item>hub</item>
<item goed="ja">switch</item>
<item>router</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 19 -->
<!--
<exercise>
<vraag>
A router uses IP addresses to forward traffic from one network to other networks.
</vraag>
</exercise>
-->

<!-- Vraag 20 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A network specialist has been hired to install a network in a company that
assembles airplane engines. Because of the nature of the business, the area is
highly affected by electromagnetic interference. Which type of network media
should be recommended so that the data communication will not be affected by
EMI?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>STP</item>
<item>coaxial</item>
<item goed="ja">fiber optic</item>
<item>UTP</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 21 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which term describes a type of coaxial cable?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">RG-6</item>
<item>568A</item>
<item>UTP</item>
<item>Cat 5e</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 22 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which pairs of wires change termination order
between the 568A and 568B standards?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">green and orange</item>
<item>green and brown</item>
<item>blue and brown</item>
<item>brown and orange</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 23 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two types of signal interference are
reduced more by STP than by UTP? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">RFI</item>
<item>white noise</item>
<item>MDF</item>
<item>dispersion</item>
<item goed="ja">EMI</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 24 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
How many host addresses are available on a
network with a subnet mask of 255.255.0.0?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">65,534</item>
<item>254</item>
<item>16,777,214</item>
<item>1024</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
256*256-2=65534
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 25 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is troubleshooting a problem where the user claims access to the
Internet is not working, but there was access to the Internet the day before. Upon
investigation, the technician determines that the user cannot access the network
printer in the office either. The network printer is on the same network as the
computer. The computer has 169.254.100.88 assigned as an IP address. What is
the most likely problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">The computer cannot communicate with a DHCP server.</item>
<item>The IP default gateway on the computer is incorrect.</item>
<item>The network interface card driver needs to be updated.</item>
<item>The router that connects this network to other networks is down.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 26 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is a characteristic of the UDP protocol?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">low overhead</item>
<item>guaranteed delivery</item>
<item>error correction</item>
<item>end-to-end establishment before delivery</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Hoofdstuk 8 -->
<!-- Vraag 1 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user notices that the data transfer rate for the gigabit NIC in the user computer
is much slower than expected. What is a possible cause for the problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
The NIC duplex settings have somehow been set to half-duplex.
</item>
<item>The NIC wake-on-LAN setting is misconfigured.</item>
<item>Hibernation mode is causing the NIC to shutdown unexpectedly.</item>
<item>The NIC is configured to use both IPv4 and IPv6 at the same time.</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
<p>
Wake-on-LAN is een optie die het mogelijk maakt om een computer vanaf
afstand uit stand-by te halen.
</p>
<p>
Hibernation zal de gehele computer afsluiten, er zal dus sowieso geen data
transfer zijn.
</p>
<p>
Het is prima mogelijk om IPv4 en IPv6 tegelijkertijd te gebruiken.
</p>
<p>
Half-duplex mode zal de snelheid flink doen verlagen ten opzichte van
full-duplex mode omdat er niet gelijktijdig gezend en ontvangen kan
worden.
</p>
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 2 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Two LEDs are usually present on a NIC. What are
the two primary uses for these LEDs? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">to indicate the presence of a connection</item>
<item>
to indicate interference from another nearby wireless or electronic device
</item>
<item>to indicate that the NIC has connected to a DHCP server</item>
<item>
to indicate that the NIC is connected to a homegroup or workgroup
</item>
<item goed="ja">to indicate that data transfer activity is present</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 3 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the purpose of the network profiles that are used
to establish a new network connection on a Windows PC?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
to configure NIC settings for the fastest network available
</item>
<item>
to remove the need for IP addresses when connecting to a network
</item>
<item>
to provide a list of ISPs that may be used for Internet access
</item>
<item goed="ja">
to provide an easy way to configure or apply network
functions based on the type of network to be joined
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 4 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A wireless router is displaying the IP address
of 192.168.0.1. What could this mean?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
The NAT function is not working on the wireless router.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
The wireless router still has the factory default IP address.
</item>
<item>
Dynamic IP address allocation has been configured on the router and is functioning
correctly.
</item>
<item>
The wireless router has been configured to use the frequencies on channel 1.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 5 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is configuring the channel on a wireless router to either 1, 6, or 11.
What is the purpose of adjusting the channel?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>to disable broadcasting of the SSID</item>
<item>to enable different 802.11 standards</item>
<item>to provide stronger security modes</item>
<item goed="ja">to avoid interference from nearby wireless devices</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 6 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which combination of user account and network location
profile allows a user to become a member of a homegroup?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
an admin account with a network location profile of Work
</item>
<item>a guest account with a network location profile of Home</item>
<item>an admin user account with a network location of Public</item>
<item goed="ja">
a standard user account with a network location profile of Home
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 7 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A business traveler connects to a wireless network with open authentication.
What should the traveler do to secure confidential data when connecting to the
business services?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Connect with a VPN.</item>
<item>Change the network location profile to public.</item>
<item>Change the Windows firewall settings.</item>
<item>
Manually configure an IP address, subnet mask, and default gateway.
</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
<p>
VPN wordt gebruikt om een versleutelde tunnel te maken naar een ander netwerk,
dit wordt veel gebruikt om het bedrijfsnetwerk vanaf elders te bereiken.
</p>
<p>
Het netwerk profiel op public zetten zal enkel wat triviale diensten
uitzetten.
</p>
<p>
Het is niet de bedoeling om handmatig de IP configuratie in te stellen
op een open wifi netwerk, dit zal ook geen zin hebben.
</p>
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 8 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician has been asked to configure a broadband connection for a
teleworker. The technician has been instructed that all uploads and downloads for
the connection must use existing phone lines. Which broadband technology
should be used?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>cable</item>
<item goed="ja">DSL</item>
<item>ISDN</item>
<item>POTS</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
kabelinternet maakt geen gebruik van telefoonlijnen. ISDN en POTS/PSTN maken
wel gebruik van telefoonlijnen, maar zijn geen breedband.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 9 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which type of connection to the Internet is capable of the fastest transfer rates?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>ISDN</item>
<item>POTS</item>
<item>satellite</item>
<item>cable</item>
<item goed="ja">fiber</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 10 -->
<exercise>
<vraag>
Which technology would be recommended for a business that requires workers to
access the Internet while visiting customers at many different locations?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>ADSL</item>
<item goed="ja">cellular</item>
<item>ISDN</item>
<item>VPN</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
De vraag is op dusdanige manier geformuleerd dat je doet denken dat VPN het
goede antwoord moet zijn, maar ze vragen enkel wat je nodig hebt om overal
toegang tot het internet te kunnen hebben, en dat is cellular.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 11 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
A small company is considering moving many of its data center functions
to the cloud. What are three advantages of this plan? (Choose three.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
The company only needs to pay for the amount of
processing and storage capacity that it uses.
</item>
<item>
Cloud services are billed at a fixed fee no matter how
much processing and storage are used by the company.
</item>
<item>
Cloud services enable the company to own and administer its own servers and storage
devices.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
The company can increase processing and storage capacity as needed and then
decrease capacity when it is no longer needed.
</item>
<item>
Single-tenant data centers can easily grow to accommodate increasing data storage
requirements.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
As the amount of data that the company uses increases, it becomes impractical for the
data to be stored and processed in a single-tenant data center.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 12 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which Cloud computing service would be best for an organization that does not
have the technical knowledge to host and maintain applications at their local site?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">SaaS</item>
<item>IaaS</item>
<item>PaaS</item>
<item>ITaaS</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 13 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A network client in a corporate environment reboots. Which type of server would
most likely be used first?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>DNS</item>
<item goed="ja">DHCP</item>
<item>e-mail</item>
<item>FTP</item>
<item>Telnet</item>
<item>Web</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
DHCP is nodig om een IP adres te verkrijgen. Zonder IP adres kunnen
andere diensten op het netwerk niet gebruikt worden.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 14 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is a common function of a proxy server?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
to store frequently accessed web pages on the internal network
</item>
<item>to control who is permitted to access the internal network</item>
<item>
to detect malicious signatures by monitoring
traffic that is entering the internal network
</item>
<item>
to provide access to a shared pool of configurable computing resources
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 15 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
ABC Company requires preventive maintenance for all local network cabling once
a year. Which task should be included in the preventive maintenance program?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Disconnect and reconnect all patch cables.</item>
<item goed="ja">Inspect all patch cables for breaks.</item>
<item>Replace all labeling on the cables.</item>
<item>
Replace all cable supports to prevent loose attachment points.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 16 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is a benefit of performing preventative maintenance at regular intervals?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">reduction in network downtime</item>
<item>reduction in connectivity</item>
<item>reduction in security threats</item>
<item>reduction in EMI and RFI</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 17 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user cannot access the network. While the technician is checking the computer,
the other users on the same network report that they are having the same
problem. Further investigation shows that the LED lights on each NIC are not lit.
What should the technician do next?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
Check each computer to verify that they all have the same settings.
</item>
<item goed="ja">Report the problem to the network administrator.</item>
<item>Attempt to ping devices on other networks.</item>
<item>Use nslookup to check network connectivity.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 18 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user can print to a printer that is on the same network, but the traffic
of the user cannot reach the Internet. What is a possible cause of the
problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
The PC default gateway address is missing or incorrect.
</item>
<item>The PC has an incorrect IP address.</item>
<item>The network cable connected to the user PC is faulty.</item>
<item>The NIC on the PC is faulty.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 19 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is investigating a report that a computer is unable to access network
resources. The technician discovers that the computer has an IP address of
169.254.27.168. What is a logical first step in diagnosing this problem?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Attempt to ping the default gateway.</item>
<item goed="ja">Check the NIC LED lights.</item>
<item>Test that DNS is operating correctly.</item>
<item>Activate Network Discovery and File Sharing.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 20 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A Windows 7 computer is unable to reach a mapped drive on a file server that is
on another network within the organization. Further investigation shows that the
user is able to use a printer that is connected to the same network as the
computer. Which action should the technician perform next?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
Verify that DNS name resolution is operating properly.</item>
<item>Inspect the network patch cable for wear or breaks.</item>
<item goed="ja">
Check Network Connection Details in the Windows GUI for the appropriate network
connection.
</item>
<item>Check the link LED on the NIC.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 21 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
A user has taken a personal laptop to work. The laptop is unable to discover the
name of the office wireless network. What are two potential causes of this
problem? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">The wireless router is not broadcasting the SSID.</item>
<item>The laptop has not received an IP address from the wireless router.</item>
<item>The wireless router is set to mixed mode.</item>
<item goed="ja">
The network does not support the wireless protocol in use by the laptop.
</item>
<item>The laptop must be configured with the office workgroup name.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 22 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A network technician attempts to ping www.example.net from a customer
computer, but the ping fails. Access to mapped network drives and a shared
printer are working correctly. What are two potential causes for this problem?
(Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
The Windows domain or workgroup name that
is configured on the computer is incorrect.
</item>
<item>The target web server is down.</item>
<item>The computer has been assigned a static IP address.</item>
<item goed="ja">DNS service is unavailable on the customer network.</item>
<item>
The HTTP protocol is not working properly on the target server.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 23 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician uses the nbtstat -A 192.168.0.3 command. What does the technician
expect to view in the command output?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">current connections and statistics</item>
<item>network adapter configuration information</item>
<item>a list of routers within the traffic path</item>
<item>computer accounts and domain specific information
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Hoofdstuk 9 -->
<!-- Vraag 1 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two statements are true of a laptop CPU
when compared to a desktop CPU? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Laptop CPUs operate at higher clock speeds.</item>
<item goed="ja">Laptop CPUs use smaller cooling devices.</item>
<item>Laptop CPUs consume more power.</item>
<item>Laptop CPUs are interchangeable with desktop CPUs.</item>
<item goed="ja">Laptop CPUs are designed to produce less heat.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 2 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which laptop component makes use of throttling
to reduce power consumption and heat?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">CPU</item>
<item>motherboard</item>
<item>optical drive</item>
<item>hard drive</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 3 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>Why are SODIMMs well suited for laptops?</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">They have a small form factor.</item>
<item>They connect to external ports.</item>
<item>They do not produce heat.</item>
<item>They are interchangeable with desktops.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 4 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is a characteristic of laptop motherboards?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
Laptop motherboards use the same form factors as desktop motherboards.
</item>
<item goed="ja">Laptop motherboards are proprietary.</item>
<item>Laptop motherboards use standard form factors.</item>
<item>
Laptop motherboard components are compatible with desktop motherboards.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 5 -->
<exercise>
<vraag>
Which laptop component converts DC power to AC power?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>fluorescent tube</item>
<item goed="ja">inverter</item>
<item>power supply</item>
<item>backlight</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 6 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Where is a Wi-Fi antenna commonly located on a laptop?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>on an external USB adapter</item>
<item goed="ja">above the laptop screen</item>
<item>next to the keyboard</item>
<item>on the side of the laptop</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 7 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
Which two methods can be used to configure
laptop ACPI power options? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">BIOS settings</item>
<item goed="ja">Windows Power Options utility</item>
<item>Windows UAC settings</item>
<item>Windows AERO theme settings</item>
<item>power dial</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 8 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user needs to connect a Bluetooth device to a laptop. Which type of cable is
needed to accomplish this?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">None. Bluetooth connections are wireless.</item>
<item>VGA cable</item>
<item>USB cable</item>
<item>EIA/TIA 232 cable</item>
<item>parallel cable</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 9 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician has installed a wireless Ethernet card in a Windows 7 laptop. Where
would the technician configure a new wireless connection?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
Control Panel > Networking and Sharing Center > Set up a new connection or network
</item>
<item>
Control Panel > Administrative Tools > Services
</item>
<item>
Control Panel > Internet Options
</item>
<item>
Control Panel > System > Device Manager
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 10 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which technology provides laptops the ability to function on a cellular network?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">mobile hotspot</item>
<item>Bluetooth</item>
<item>infrared</item>
<item>802.11 Wi-Fi</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 11 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician is trying to remove a SODIMM module from a laptop. What is the
correct way to do this?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
Press outward on the clips that hold the sides of the SODIMM.
</item>
<item>
Pull outward by holding the center of the SODIMM module.
</item>
<item>Apply downward force on the SODIMM module.</item>
<item>Desolder the SODIMM module.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 12 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
When replacing or adding memory to a laptop, where can a technician
find the maximum amount of RAM each memory slot can support?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>BIOS</item>
<item>System Properties window</item>
<item>POST screen</item>
<item goed="ja">website of manufacturer</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
De maximale hoeveelheid RAM die ondersteund wordt, wordt
bepaald door het moederbord.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 13 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What should be done immediately after a CPU is
latched in and screwed down to a laptop motherboard?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
The heat sink should be attached to the CPU.
</item>
<item>
The cooling fan should be fastened to the motherboard.
</item>
<item>
The power cable should be attached from the cooling fan to the motherboard.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
The locked down CPU should be protected with thermal paste.
</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
De geleiding van warmte tussen de CPU en het koelblok gaat niet over
100% van het oppervlak door minimale oneffenheden. Koelpasta helpt
deze oneffenheden op te vullen om toch wat geleiding te krijgen. De
beste koelpasta zal echter niet zo goed geleiden als direct contact.
Let daarom op niet teveel koelpasta te gebruiken: beter te weinig
koelpasta dan te veel!
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 14 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which technology allows a mobile device to establish wireless communication
with another mobile device by touching them together?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Bluetooth</item>
<item goed="ja">NFC</item>
<item>IR</item>
<item>Lightning connector</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 15 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
Which technology will allow a mobile device to share
an Internet connection with other devices via tethering?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>infrared</item>
<item goed="ja">Bluetooth</item>
<item>near field communication</item>
<item>Wi-Fi</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
Het goede antwoord is aangegeven als Bluetooth, maar infra-rood
en Wi-Fi zijn wel degelijk methodes om tethering toe te passen.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 16 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What are two differences between an e-reader and a tablet device? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>
An e-reader only supports Wi-Fi connectivity but a
tablet can support both Wi-Fi and cellular connectivity.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
An e-reader commonly has longer battery life than a tablet device.
</item>
<item>
A tablet device is usually lighter in weight than an e-reader.
</item>
<item goed="ja">
A tablet device screen may be harder to read
in direct sunlight than an e-reader screen.
</item>
<item>
A tablet uses an electronic paper technology that
provides better performance than an e-reader.
</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 17 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What type of device is commonly used to measure and
collect daily activity data for achieving personal goals?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>phablet</item>
<item>smart camera</item>
<item goed="ja">fitness monitor</item>
<item>Global Positioning System</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 18 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
A technician has been asked to decide which laptop components should be
cleaned on a monthly basis as part of a maintenance routine. What are two
examples of components that should be included? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">exterior case</item>
<item goed="ja">keyboard</item>
<item>CPU</item>
<item>optical drive</item>
<item>RAM</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 19 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
To clean laptops, which two products are recommended? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">cotton swabs</item>
<item goed="ja">mild cleaning solution</item>
<item>ammonia</item>
<item>rubbing alcohol</item>
<item>car wax</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 20 -->
<exercise type="multi">
<vraag>
What two steps must be taken before performing a cleaning procedure on a laptop
computer? (Choose two.)
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">
Disconnect the laptop from the electrical outlet.
</item>
<item goed="ja">Remove all installed batteries.</item>
<item>Wipe the surface of the touch pad.</item>
<item>Clean the screen with a cloth.</item>
<item>Insert the cleaning disk into the optical drive.</item>
<item>Backup the registry.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 21 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the first step in the process of troubleshooting a laptop?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">Identify the problem.</item>
<item>Establish probable causes.</item>
<item>Determine the exact cause.</item>
<item>Verify full functionality.</item>
</choice>
<toelichting>
Uiteraard moet je eerst weten wat het probleem is voor je het
probeert op te lossen.
</toelichting>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 22 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
What is the next step in the troubleshooting process
after a solution has been implemented on a laptop?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Verify the solution.</item>
<item goed="ja">Document the solution.</item>
<item>Ask the customer to explain the problem.</item>
<item>Return the device to the customer.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 23 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
While troubleshooting a mobile device, a technician determines that the battery
is not holding a charge. What is the next step in the troubleshooting process?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Implement a solution.</item>
<item>Document the findings.</item>
<item goed="ja">Determine the exact cause.</item>
<item>Verify the solution and full system functionality.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 24 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A technician notices that a laptop display appears stretched
and pixelated. What is a probable cause of this?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item goed="ja">The display properties are incorrectly set.</item>
<item>The power management features are incorrectly set.</item>
<item>The power inverter is failing.</item>
<item>The screen has been burned in.</item>
<item>One of the RAM modules is failing.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

<!-- Vraag 25 -->
<exercise type="single">
<vraag>
A user with a company-issued smartphone notices that there is a gap at the end of
the device. A technician examines the smartphone and discovers that the battery
is swollen. What should the technician do next?
</vraag>
<choice>
<item>Use the smartphone until the battery is completely discharged.</item>
<item>Clean the battery leads with baking soda.</item>
<item goed="ja">Replace the battery.</item>
<item>Use a multimeter to see if the output voltage is within range.</item>
</choice>
</exercise>

</exam>



